Preliminary Guide to the Gelman Library, Slavic, East European, and Asian Reading Room records, 1962-1995 RG0132
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Gelman Library, Slavic, East European, and Asian Reading Room records
1962-1995
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
RG0132
52.5 Linear Feet
This collection contains correspondence, foundation proposals, grants, conference reports, articles and papers, research fellows, exchange participants, research assistants. The material relates to the workings of the Reading Room. This material dates from 1962-95.
Restrictions on Access
Series 1 is closed to research for 50 years from date of record creation.
Acquisition Information
Acquisition data is unknown.
Historical or Biographical Note
The Slavic, East European, and Asian Reading Room is a reference and research collection focusing primarily on the post World War II political, economic, and military affairs of the Russian Federation, Ukraine, the Czech Republic, Slovakia, China, Taiwan, Japan, and Korea. It was formerly known as the Sino-Soviet Information Center.
Collection Scope and Content
This collection contains correspondence, foundation proposals, grants, conference reports, articles and papers, research fellows, exchange participants, research assistants. The material relates to the workings of the Reading Room. This material dates from 1962-95.
Collection Organization
Organized into two series both titled Office files.
Soviet Union; Radio programs; Students for a Democratic Society (U.S.); Maury Hall; Research
- Office files, 1980-1989; RG0132 Series 1; 16.5 Linear feet
  Scope and Contents note
  This series contains Sino-Soviet Center files. These materials date from 1980-89 and cover such topics as the Soviet Interview Project, Harvard project materials, correspondence, films, general survey codebook.
  Formerly ACC#526
  This series has a container list in electronic form, please ask staff for assistance.
- Office files, 1962-1995; RG0132 Series 2; 36 Linear feet
  This series contains foundation proposals, grants, conference reports, articles and papers, correspondence, research fellows, exchange participants, research assistants, SDS attack on the Institute (1969), WTOP radio programs hosted by Kurt London (director). This material dates from 1962-95.
  Formerly ACC#698
  - American Council of Learned Societies: Conference on Changes in the Status of Women in Eastern Europe, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Asia Foundation, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - American Council of Learned Societies, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    General note
    Wolchik/Skomal, denied
  - Bradley Foundation, 1986-1989 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Correspondence to/from Franz Michael
  - Carnegie Foundation, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Carnegie Foundation: Library Support, 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Carthage Foundation, 07/01/1972-06/30/1977 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Edna McConnell Clark Foundation, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Denied
  - Council on Religion and International Affairs, NY, 07/17/1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Correspondence to Gaston Sigur from Bob Myers
  - Donner Foundation, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Donner Foundation, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Donner Foundation: Request, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Earhart Foundation, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Proposal, Japan
  - Earhart Foundation, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Papers, 658-130
  - Earhart Foundation, 1966-1971 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Correspondence
  - Earhart Foundation, 1978-1989 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Earhart Foundation, 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Correspondence, information, Japan Study, 638-130
  - Earhart Foundation, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    faculty salary support, 758-720
  - Earhart Foundation, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    salary support and fellowships, 758-21
  - Earhart Foundation, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Research and fellowship support, 758-22
  - Earhart Foundation, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Research and fellowship support
  - Earhart Foundation, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Linden salary support
  - Earhart Foundation, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    report on graduate fellowship support
  - Earhart Foundation, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    graduate student support
  - Earhart Foundation, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    758-420, fellowships
  - Earhart Foundation, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    tuition grant, 758-726
  - Earhart Foundation, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    758-430, fellowships
  - Earhart Foundation: Conference, Soviet-Chinese Policy in Asia, 003/1979 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    758-421
  - Earhart Foundation: Conference, East Asia and Problems of Detente, 007/1979 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    758-725
  - Earhart Foundation: Professor Petrov's trip to People's Republic of China, 005/1980 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    758-727
  - Earhart Foundation, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Grant, Gelber, 758-727
  - Earhart Foundation: Soviet Conference, 005/1981 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    758-728
  - Earhart Foundation: Radio Free Europe, 005/1982 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    758-732
  - Earhart Foundation, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    758-19722, fellowships
  - Earhart Foundation, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    758-19729, Jonathan Chaves, academic year
  - Earhart Foundation, 004/1982 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Dr. Kim
  - Earhart Foundation, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    758-19731, fellowships
  - Earhart Foundation: Conference on Mainland China, Airlie House, 006/1983 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    708/720
  - Earhart Foundation: Soviet Conference, 005/1983 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    758-721
  - Earhart Foundation, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Earhart Foundation, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    758-19723, AU79416, fellowships
  - Earhart Foundation: Soviet Conference, 006/1985 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    7508/725, AU79418
  - Earhart Foundation, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    fellowships, 758-19724, AU79417
  - Earhart Foundation, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    fellowships, AU79419
  - Earhart Foundation: 5th Joint Conference on Peace and Security in Asia, 009/1987 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    AU99420
  - Earhart Foundation, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    fellowships, AU79420
  - Earhart Foundation: China and the Crisis of Marxism-Leninism, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    Franz Michael, AU09415
  - Earhart Foundation, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    AU79421, fellowships
  - Earhart Foundation, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    request for fellowship support, denied
  - East Asian Studies/ACAPA agreement, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    RU03414
  - Expo Fund, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Exxon Education Corporation Request, 002/1981 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Far Eastern Textile Corporation: Funds for conference of East Asian Security, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Ford Foundation, 1962-1971 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Ford Foundation, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Ford Foundation: Financial information, 1963-1971 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Ford Foundation: Kuhlman request, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Ford Foundation proposal, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Ford Foundation Conference: East Asia and Problems of Detente, 007/1979 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    758-730
  - Ford Foundation Proposal: Conference, Women in Eastern Europe, 007/1980 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Ford Foundation: Women's Conference, 102/1981 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Ford Foundation, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Foundation Request: Letters, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Fulbright-Hayes Fellowship: H. L. Millar, 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Glenmede/PEW Charitable Trusts, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    Miscellaneous correspondence
  - Glenmede Trust Company, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    General correspondence
  - Glenmede: Correspondence, \1 ca.1979 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Glenmede Trust Company/PEW: Award, 09/29/1972 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Glenmede Trust Company/PEW: Request, 10/1973 (Box 1, Folder 69)
    denied
  - Glenmede Trust Company/PEW: Award, 03/12/1975 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Glenmede Trust Company/PEW: Award, 03/01/1976 (Box 1, Folder 71)
    758-740
  - Glenmede Trust Company/PEW: Award, 04/27/1977 (Box 1, Folder 72)
    758-741
  - Glenmede Trust Company/PEW, 03/02/1978 (Box 1, Folder 73)
    $12,000 awarded for 1978-1979
  - Glenmede Trust Company/PEW: Award, 05/1979 (Box 1, Folder 74)
    758-743
  - Glenmede Trust Company/PEW:, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 75)
    758-739
  - Glenmede Trust Company/PEW:, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 76)
    758-744
  - Glenmede Trust Company/PEW:, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 77)
    758-745
  - Glenmede Trust Company/PEW:, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 78)
    758-746
  - Glenmede Trust Company/PEW:, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 79)
    AU79451, correspondence, grant proposal
  - Glenmede Trust Company/PEW, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 80)
    Final report and other correspondence
  - Glenmede Trust Company/PEW: Final report, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Glenmede Trust Company/PEW: Final report, 07/01/1986-06/30/1987 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Glenmede - GWU joint proposal: Program for Integrated Economy and National Security, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Glenmede Trust Company/PEW, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Proposal
  - Glenmede/Pew Charitable Trust, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Proposal to resubmit at conclusion of current grant
  - Glenmede/Pew Charitable Trust: Intra-University correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    AU99462, grant
  - Glenmede Trust Company/Pew: Proposal, 1989-90 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    multi- and bi-lateral conferences, and final narrative and financial reports
  - Grevey Foundation request, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Denied 03/1988
  - Gulf Oil: William Scott, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Project on the USSR
  - Gulf Oil: Northeast Asia Center in Institute for European, Russian, and Eurasian Studies, 04/11/1977 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Hoffman, George donation in support of the Balkan Project, 07/09/1990 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Hyundai: Korean Books, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Gelman Library
  - Hyundai, 1982-1984 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    correspondence
  - Hyundai, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    background
  - International Communication Agency, 11/12/1980 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    denial of proposal for 2nd Joint Conference on Peace/Security in Asia
  - International Research and Exchange Board travel grant/Sigur, 09/1977 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    759-19730
  - International Research and Exchange Board grant: East Asia and Problems of Detente, 07/1979 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    759-735
  - International Research and Exchange Board proposal: Soviet conference in1981, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - International Research and Exchange Board proposal: Soviet conference, 08/1982 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - International Research and Exchange Board grant: Women's ConferenceWolchik, 12/1981 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    759-741
  - International Research and Exchange Board grant: Dr. Kim, Soviet Union, 05/1982 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    759-742
  - International Research and Exchange Board: Soviet Conference, 05/1983 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    759-19744
  - Japan American Society, 11/1986 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Japan Program proposal, 04/1978 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Japan-United States Friendship Committee proposal, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Japanese Studies Program, 04/1973 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Japan Society Proposal, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Japan proposal: Sigur/Johnson, 11/1981 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Japan Foundation proposal, 1975-1978 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Japan Foundation proposal, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Japan Foundation proposal: Kimura, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - US-Japan Program for the Study of Global Problems: Scalera, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Japan-U.S. Friendship Commission, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    790-19752, AU77606
  - Japan-U.S. Friendship Commission, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    AU77605, correspondence and grant agreement
  - Japan-U.S. Friendship Commission, 02/1985-06/30/1985 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    AU77607, 750-19793, correspondence
  - Japan-U.S. Friendship Commission, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    grant proposal AU16030
  - Japan-U.S. Study Project: Background, 1982-1984 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    funded by U.S. Japan Foundation and Japan-U.S. Friendship Commission
  - Japanese Embassy, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - W.K. Kellogg Foundation, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Korean Institute of International Relations, 12/1981 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Korean Ministry of Education, 05/1982 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Korea Research Foundation, 1982-1986 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Korean Fellowships: Hankuk Glass Company, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Korean Air funding proposal, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    No response
  - Korean Traders Scholarship Foundation, 03/1982 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Kosuth Foundation/Wolchik/Skomal, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Kyonggi University, Korea, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    agreement and financial information
  - Lilly Endowment request, 02/1981 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Lilly Endowment Proposals, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    Also includes year 1976
  - Lozansky, Edward: Program on East-West Relations in the Era of Glasnost, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    no action
  - Mott, Charles Stewart Foundation, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Mitsui and Co. (U.S.A.) Inc: funds, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - National Council on Soviet and East European Research: Wolchik, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - National Council on Soviet and East European Research: Freidzon, 10/1986 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - National Council on Soviet and East European Research: Freidzon, 11/1987 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - National Council on Soviet and East European Research: Freidzon, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - National Council on Soviet and East European Research: Wolchik, 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    659-180
  - National Council on Soviet and East European Research: Sodaro, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    AU29610
  - National Council on Soviet and East European Research, 07/1978 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities: Wolchik/Skomal, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - O'Donnell Fund, 1971-1974 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - John M. Olin Foundation request, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - John M. Olin Foundation request, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Pentel, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Reader's Digest, 02/1981 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Relm Foundation: Student Fellowships, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    Also includes yeard 1975-1978
  - Relm Foundation grant: Dr. Toru Yano, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Relm Foundation grants, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Relm Foundation grants, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Relm Foundation grants, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Scaife Family Charitable Trusts: Grant history, 01/1978-05/1987 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Scaife Report, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Scaife Report, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Scaife Report, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Scaife Report, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Scaife Report, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Scaife Report, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Scaife Report, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Scaife Report, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Scaife Report, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Scaife Report, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Scaife, 1976-1986 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    non-proposal correspondence
  - Scaife, 09/18/1978 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    request for 3 years, 007/001/1979-006/300/1982
  - Scaife: Request, 01/19/1990 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    Johnson as Director of the East Asian Studies Program
  - Scaife Request, 1987-90 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Scaife grant: $75,000, 12/05/1985 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Scaife Request, 03/21/1984 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    For 2 years, 007/001/1984 - 006/300/1986
  - Scaife: $100,000 proposal and award, 07/01/1982-06/30/1984 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Scaife Proposal, 11/1975 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    for 3 years, 007/001/1976 - 006/300/1979
  - Scaife: Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Scaife: General correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Scaife: Proposals, awards, reports, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    758-770
  - Scaife:general correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Sloan, Alfred P., Foundation, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Smith Richardson Foundation, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Smith Richardson Foundation, 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Smith Richardson Foundation: Aksyonov, 06/1982 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - State Department: Conference on Eastern Europe in the 1980s, 04/1980-05/1980 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    758-760
  - State Department: Lewis, Refugees, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - State Department: Nuclear Non-Proliferation Symposium, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Lewis, 750-700
  - State Department, 06/1984 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Television News Center - GW, 1977-1980 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Toyota Fund Proposal, 06/1978 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Through Policy Studies
  - United States Information Agency contract: IA 17393-23, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    750-735
  - United States Information Agency contract: IA 17827-24, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    750-745
  - United States Information Agency proposal for technology transfer project, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - United States Information Agency proposal: Fund the 3rd Soviet Conference on Peace and Security in Asia, 05/1983 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - United States Information Agency proposal: Fund 12th Sino-American Conference on Mainland China, 06/1983 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - United States Information Agency proposal: Thornton, Lewis, Salzburg Dialogues, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - United States Information Agency proposal: Tropea/Sociology, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    Never sent
  - United States Information Agency/US-Japan Study Project, undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - United States Information Agency: Global Information Revolution and East-West Relations, 10/15/1987 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Through SIA, rejected
  - US Arms Control and Disarmament Agency: Lewis, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - US-Japan Foundation proposal: Albrecht, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    Revised by Lewis, denied
  - U.S. Japan Foundation: Nau, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - U.S. Japan Foundation:US Japan Economic Agenda, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - U.S. Japan Foundation: US-Japan Study Project information, 1982-1987 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - U.S. Japan Foundation: US-Japan Study Project, 1982-1987 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    financial information
  - U.S. Japan Agenda, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Wenner-Gren Foundation: Wolchik/Skomal, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Weinig, Sheldon: Japanese Training Programs, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    Nothing materialized
  - WTOP Radio: The Communist World (K. London), 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    Lecturers R. Allen, R. Boyd
  - WTOP Radio: The Communist World (K. London), 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    Lecturers M.Gaster, B. Fall, O. Caldwell
  - WTOP Radio: The Communist World (K. London), 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    Lecturers P.Han, P.Gekker
  - WTOP Radio: The Communist World (K. London), 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    Lecturers G.Kousoulas, J.Karch, H.Hinton
  - WTOP Radio: The Communist World (K. London), 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    Lecturers K.London, M.Lindsay
  - WTOP Radio: The Communist World (K. London), 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    "The Communist World Today: Change or Erosion"
  - WTOP Radio: The Communist World (K. London), 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    Lecturers B.Maday, L.Metzl, T.McNelly
  - WTOP Radio: The Communist World (K. London), 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    Lecturers M.Jur, B.Nimer, F.Michael, B.Overstreet
  - WTOP Radio: The Communist World (K. London), 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    Lecturers G. Overstreet, B. Overstreet, B.Ramuda
  - WTOP Radio: The Communist World (K. London), 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    Lecturers R. Thornton, R. Thompson, W. Roberts
  - WTOP Radio: The Communist World (K. London), 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    Lecturers H.Yakobson, T.Wolfe, R.White
  - WTOP Radio: The Communist World (K. London), 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    Lecturers A. Dasbach,Ch. Elliott, H. Hinton
  - WTOP Radio: The Communist World (K. London), 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    Lecturers G. Kousoulas, K. London, B. Maday
  - WTOP Radio: The Communist World (K. London), 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    Lecturers Th.McNelly, V.Petrov
  - WTOP Radio: The Communist World (K. London), 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    Lecturers B.Ramundo, B. Reich, R. Renfield
  - WTOP Radio: The Communist World (K. London), 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    Lecturers J. Thomas, L. Szalay, W.Roberts
  - WTOP Radio: The Communist World (K. London), 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    Lecturers R. White, Th. Thornton,J. Thomas
  - WTOP Radio: The Communist World (K. London), 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    Lecturers K. Chung, D. Cattellj. Armstrong
  - WTOP Radio: The Communist World (K. London), 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    Lecturers G. Kousoulas, H. Hinton, J. Hardt
  - WTOP Radio, The Communist World, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    Lecturers K.London, S.Ploss
  - WTOP Radio, The Communist World, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    Lecturers H. Sachar,J.Polach,K.Ploss
  - WTOP Radio, The Communist World, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    Lecturers J. Walkin, Th. Thornton, J. Thomas
  - The United States and Eastern Europe, 05/02/1968-05/05/1968 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Program, Participants, Agenda
  - Fourth Sino-American Conference on Mainland China [1/6], 12/12/1974-12/15/1974 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Papers and Comments
  - Fourth Sino-American Conference on Mainland China [2/6], 12/12/1974-12/15/1974 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Fourth Sino-American Conference on Mainland China [3/6], 12/12/1974-12/15/1974 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Fourth Sino-American Conference on Mainland China [4/6], 12/12/1974-12/15/1974 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Fourth Sino-American Conference on Mainland China [5/6], 12/12/1974-12/15/1974 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Fourth Sino-American Conference on Mainland China [6/6], 12/12/1974-12/15/1974 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Fourth Sino-American Conference on Mainland China, 12/12/1974-12/15/1974 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Program Information
  - Fourth Sino-American Conference on Mainland China, 12/12/1974-12/15/1974 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Financial Information
  - Korea and the Major Powers [1/4], 05/01/1975-05/03/1975 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Korea and the Major Powers [2/4], 05/01/1975-05/03/1975 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Korea and the Major Powers [3/4], 05/01/1975-05/03/1975 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Korea and the Major Powers [4/4], 05/01/1975-05/03/1975 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Korea and the Major Powers, 05/01/1975-05/03/1975 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Budget
  - Korea and the Major Powers, 05/01/1975-05/03/1975 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Agenda and Participants
  - U.S. Policy toward Asian-Pacific Area [1/4], 10/03/1975-10/04/1975 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    Papers
  - U.S. Policy toward Asian-Pacific Area [2/4], 10/03/1975-10/04/1975 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - U.S. Policy toward Asian-Pacific Area [3/4], 10/03/1975-10/04/1975 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - U.S. Policy toward Asian-Pacific Area [4/4], 10/03/1975-10/04/1975 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - U.S. Policy toward Asian-Pacific Area, 10/03/1975-10/04/1975 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    Participants, Discussion, and Summary
  - Dimensions of Sino-American Relations [1/2], 12/16/1976-12/18/1976 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Dimensions of Sino-American Relations [1/2], 12/16/1976-12/18/1976 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Dimensions of Sino-American Relations, 12/16/1976-12/18/1976 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    Program, Participants, Financial Info
  - Innovation in Communist Systems, 04/29/1977-4/30/1977 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Innovation in Communist Systems, 04/29/1977-4/30/1977 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Mid-Atlantic Regional Meeting of the Association for Asian Studies, 10/28/1978-10/29/1978 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    Program and Background Information
  - East Asia and Problems of Detente, 07/09/1978-07/13/1978 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    Pre and Post-Correspondence